[
  { 
    "id": 1,
    "title": "Português",
    "questions": [
      { "id": 1, "question": "1- Qual preço da batata?", "answer": "1- R$ 27,50" },
      { "id": 2, "question": "2- Qual a formula da água?", "answer": "2- H2O" },
      { "id": 3, "question": "3- Qual teu nome?", "answer": "3- Greg" },
      { "id": 4, "question": "4- Quantos X pra trocar 1 lâmpada", "answer": "4- depende" },
      { "id": 5, "question": "5- Era ____ vez", "answer": "5- 'uma'" },
      { "id": 6, "question": "6- 2x2", "answer": "6- 4" }
    ]
  },
  { 
    "id": 2,
    "title": "História",
    "questions": [
      { "id": 1, "question": "1- Qual preço da batata?", "answer": "1- R$ 27,50" },
      { "id": 2, "question": "2- Qual a formula da água?", "answer": "2- H2O" },
      { "id": 3, "question": "3- Qual teu nome?", "answer": "3- Greg" },
      { "id": 4, "question": "4- Quantos X pra trocar 1 lâmpada", "answer": "4- depende" },
      { "id": 5, "question": "5- Era ____ vez", "answer": "5- 'uma'" },
      { "id": 6, "question": "6- 2x2", "answer": "6- 4" }
    ]
  },
  { 
    "id": 3,
    "title": "Geografia",
    "questions": [
      { "id": 1, "question": "1- Qual preço da batata?", "answer": "1- R$ 27,50" },
      { "id": 2, "question": "2- Qual a formula da água?", "answer": "2- H2O" },
      { "id": 3, "question": "3- Qual teu nome?", "answer": "3- Greg" },
      { "id": 4, "question": "4- Quantos X pra trocar 1 lâmpada", "answer": "4- depende" },
      { "id": 5, "question": "5- Era ____ vez", "answer": "5- 'uma'" },
      { "id": 6, "question": "6- 2x2", "answer": "6- 4" }
    ]
  }  
]